all right welcome to another episode of
Jackman radio and very excited tonight
to have a returning guest this is his
third time um on Jackman radio with us
it's former CIA officer author and
whistleblower and just overall good guy
John kyaku John thanks so much for
joining us tonight man hey thanks guys
my only regret is you know last time I
was on the show when we finished we went
out for a pizza and a couple of beers
and we can't do that this time yeah that
was that was great yeah we brought you
to pasta in mil yeah one of our favorite
spots spots up here up the road from we
had a studio for a minute but I was
telling John before we went live our old
producer Ricky moved back to Texas with
the family but we had some good times
there but uh God there's just so much uh
been going on in the world and I was you
know obviously we've been following the
cabinet picks that Trump has and and the
news and foreign policy and everything
and I said to Mike I said Mike we got to
get John back on the show to get his
thoughts on everything that's going on
and and of course you wrote a great
piece um that Consortium published and a
couple other places published uh just
talking a little bit about my good
friend Tulsi gabri's appointment uh
nomination to be Director of National
Intelligence by Trump so so many things
to get to but first of all John how have
you been man what have you been up to
I've been great thanks um you know I had
a radio show for a long time for seven
and a half years on Sputnik uh here in
Washington and um sanctions shut us down
with literally one hour notice it was
one hour before the show was supposed to
go on and then I had a I had a TV show
called The whistleblowers that was
wildly popular it
ran it ran in um 100 countries and uh
and that was shut down too uh
unfortunately because of sanctions the
the Biden White House was very crafty
about these sanctions they didn't
sanction the Russian media they
sanctioned the banks we use to get our
paychecks so um just the act of
receiving a paycheck was uh money
laundering and so they threw us all out
of work so in the meantime my former
colleagues um Michelle witty and Ted R
and I just started a podcast that's uh
that's on YouTube called Deep program
we're gonna change the name soon but we
just did our second episode today it
should be posted in like the next hour
or so and um I'm writing for consor I'm
writing for for uh uh cover action
magazine and I'm excited to
say that starting on January 31st I'm
GNA do a speaking tour of
Belfast uh Dublin Waterford and Cork
Ireland and Manchester England so if
anybody happens to be in Ireland wow
yeah and tickets have been for sale for
a week they're half sold half sold out
so get them
fast that's great man who's who's
putting that on it's called um tiger
Lane Studios it's a a production company
that has the most popular play in the
West End of London right now it's coming
to uh coming to Broadway in February
called um a night of
murder wow starring Hillary
[Applause]
Clinton wow that so you're going all
over John that's amaz amazing I'm
excited about it it's it's a kind of a
new thing for me a new opportunity and
they're just they're going to bring you
around to these are they like theaters
or are they yeah they're we're start in
Ireland we're starting with the hotel
ballrooms um we're going to do 50 50
dates in England and they're going to be
all theaters mostly local theaters then
we're going to go to Australia New
Zealand and then Canada then Continental
Europe and finish the year in the Middle
East
whoa that's wild I feel like you know I
feel like the Irish have a pension not
just for the drink but also for the
truth and uh he'll be well received over
there I think Mike in all seriousness I
think that is exactly right in fact um
I'm gonna give interviews to two Irish
newspapers tomorrow about the event and
they've asked very specific questions
that they they sent me a half dozen
questions just to think about so um they
are they are warriors for the truth yes
and that's exactly what they want to
discuss wow that's exciting they're not
going to be like oh you know is it is it
like is it really like James Bond is it
John you have to wear a tux when you go
on the signment
they're they're not gonna go there you
know now here I I can wear this when I
go when I go on stage huh oh there it is
guys there it is yeah we had a comment
yeah hopefully John is wearing the
infamous SpongeBob shirt he's got it
guys we saw your com it's a little worn
and I I mentioned on another podcast
that I didn't really think about the
historical significance of it so I wore
it to paint my living room one time and
I got paint all over it but you know
better late than never it lives on it's
like Old Glory yeah yeah and I watched
uh I I watched most of your debate with
Andrew bamonte man that that what a
discussion you guys are having I mean
what do you make of that guy do you
think is he is he just still currently
in he's just a PR dude or is you think
he's really out I think he's out
[Music]
um but honest to God man I I never met
somebody who was so obviously an
apologist for literally everything that
the CIA does Andrew is a nice guy I
liked him we even exchanged numbers I
like him and it was fun to debate him
but
he's irrationally Pro CIA yeah what
you're talking about was the um the
Danny Jones podcast in concrete correct
yeah that guy does a great show he's out
on John Newman he's out on Jim de eugo
all kinds of great guests yeah big big
people he gets it's it's really
something he's got hundreds of thousands
of followers and millions of views it's
a lot of fun going down there I've done
that podcast three times and he
mentioned to me over a year ago he said
hey would you be interested in debating
uh Andrew Bustamante and I said sure
that sounds like fun and then you guys
have known me long enough we've been
friends for a decade I don't prepare for
these things right because I figure if I
don't know it by now I'm not going to
learn it between now and when the
podcast starts so
um I started thinking a couple days in
advance you know this is a debate and
usually it's just John bloviating on
right so maybe maybe I should prepare
and then I thought no no I'm not going
to prepare I'm just going to do what I
always do and I got to say I'm I was
really pleased at the end of it with
with the way I I came out of it I tried
hard not to be
defensive and and he attacked me at one
point um which you a little bit yeah he
did it kind of took me by surprise but I
think in the end it all worked out he um
he spent seven years at the
agency uh as a what's called a sue a
special operations officer he was not a
case officer he was not a case officer
I'm going to say it a second time okay
um he was a an operations support
officer
so if I need somebody to do surveillance
or counter surveillance for me I need
somebody to fill out my paperwork
because I'm too busy doing other stuff
that's what those guys do he wasn't
grabbing ABAB Ban's ear wax no sir okay
and he wasn't he wasn't covert or had
cover or did he he uh he may have had
cover but he's so out there publicly now
I wonder I wonder if he ever had cover
or if it was what's called um either
notional cover which is just as needed
or nominal cover which is light light
cover where do you work I work at the
Pentagon oh okay that's light cover
right yeah no that was an interesting
chat uh tell him though John if he wants
to debate the Kennedy assassination
Governor ventor is ready to go we'll go
down together you know my feelings about
Governor Jesse vent I freaking love that
guy and his his son Tyrell is is a deep
de
friend I I just can't say enough
wonderful things about the two of them
patriots both they really are both them
yeah yeah and you want to talk Kennedy
assassination talk to Aaron good too oh
my God had him on Oh Aaron is he's
amazing as well just amazing yeah he's
he's good with the granular and and and
um uh yeah you know kind of the more
offbeat you know off the beaten P stuff
and I think Peter Dale Scott is a big
mentor of his yeah big big mentor and
another thing about Aaron too is it's
not just the JFK assassination he can go
just as deep on RFK and on Martin Luther
King he's that good yeah I think he I
think he's in that um series they
haven't released all of it but four who
died trying that came out last year they
released part one I watched part one it
was awesome yeah yeah yeah Mike you
wrote a review for for part of that
didn't you for the uh her Bobby super
pack yeah for um American values I wrote
a review for that that came out that's
the only piece I've I've written for
them thus far but um you know real
quickly let me ask you guys a question
speaking of Bobby um what do you think
about about HHS his appointment as the
secretary I think he's gonna get
it I think he's gonna get it too I feel
really good about it and not only that
John I think that Bernie and Cory Booker
are GNA vote for
him H that'll be the I on the I do I
really I think Bernie knows this is kind
of his last this is it for him he's 80
what is he like 82 83 years old3 this
year yeah yeah he's near the end of his
career yeah he's near the end of his
career um and he he can really help
promote a lot of the things that he has
in common with Bobby they're not going
to agree on everything um but I'm
feeling really good about it Bobby has
some really capable intelligent plugged
in people around him were helping him
navigate the confirmation process and
and uh I think he's going to get it I
think you know not just because he
should get it and that he's been
fighting this fight for so long but also
I think there's a lot of senators who
are they don't want to cross Maga they
don't want to cross Trump and have a
primary challenge in 2026 you know and
that's it's interesting that you say
that I I think that's exactly correct
and the reason why I also think it's
interesting is that from the moment that
Donald Trump puts his right hand in the
air on January 20th he's a lame duck so
technically nobody owes him anything
right in
reality he is just as fearsome now as he
was on January 20th
2017 and you're right nobody dares cross
him no I mean Jody Ernst just seeing her
she kind of did a quick about faceing a
180 on Heth boy did she real fast and
you know it's funny too because Heth is
actually easy to criticize and I don't
mean you know he's he cheated on all
three of his wife
and he's got a longstanding alcohol
problem that stuff in in the 2020s
doesn't matter it's it's not 1989
anymore you know welcome welcome to
Washington DC that's right and John
Tower you know oh my God John Tower was
in the senate for 36 years and we never
noticed that he womanized and drank and
then they rejected him right um yeah
time times have changed but but hex in
my view just he's not qualified to run
what is essentially a company of 3
million employees and A1 trillion budget
like there's not one guy in
America that's more qualified than Pete
hex to to handle
DOD I find that hard to believe yeah hey
we had uh Jim Webb Jr on Bobby's
campaign when I worked for him as an
adviser and I I've always thrown out Jim
web's name for anything with Trump and I
know every everybody does but I think
he's reluct to get back into the scrum
you think he's done I think he just
doesn't enjoy it yeah but that that guy
those are the people you want those are
the people you want he was a terrific
Senator when he was Junior senator from
Virginia terrific Senator and he just
didn't like it yeah he beat George Allen
right for that seed yeah he did and
George Allen was popular yeah George
Allen very popular uh but he had the
makaka moment which seems quaint now you
know yeah yeah yeah that's opening act
of a magar
rally it's the craziest thing um yeah no
those are all really good points John
and um you know Trump is going on
personality and image uh in in locker
room jocular Warrior guy who's gonna run
the Pentagon for me yeah um but if heg
Seth is gonna make it then that clears
the way for Tulsi everybody's G to make
it yeah everyone's going to make it
Gates I think Trump threw Gates out
there as a as a weather balloon as the T
it totally how far how far can I push
this thing which is also a very
Washington thing to do yeah a very
Washington thing to do yeah so in your
piece John uh the week that uh Trump
announced Tulsi um for dni um you
mentioned uh some of the haters uh rep
Abigail spanberger talking about uh
Tulsi you know of course bringing up
Assad and bringing up Putin what do you
make of the letter or uh the people like
Bolton and and the lob and the
establishment coming out against her
what do you make of that oh I I would
consider that to be a badge of honor and
I think she already does considered to
be a badge of honor you know let's for
example look at the uh at her 2017 trip
to uh to Damascus first of all members
of Congress can go literally anywhere in
the world that they want as part of of
their own personal fact finding right
you're you're a member of Congress in
her case she was serving on the armed
services committee at the time she's a
member of the majority party at the time
she's highly respected she wanted to see
the situation on the ground for
herself um now whether or not you like
uh Bashar al-assad's personal politics
God bless that's your personal business
but the truth of the matter is that
until
Saturday the Syrian government was
secular all religions and I mean that
word quite literally all religions were
free to PR practice their faith without
any interference I have been to the
synagogue in Damascus which is one of
the oldest continuously working
synagogues on the planet Earth I've been
to the Greek Orthodox Cathedral in
Damascus it was packed to the gills the
vice president of Syria was a Christian
until Saturday members of the cabinet
were Christians there are Christians and
women and minorities in the Syrian
Parliament okay now that's all out the
window
now whatever this government ends up
being in the end and we can call it Isis
or dases or Hezbollah
or or alqaeda an front alqaeda exactly
we can call it any of those things it is
not secular and it does not allow uh the
free practice of uh of faiths other than
Sunni
Islam yeah they're not going to protect
Christians protect Christians 10% of the
Syrian population is christian 10% and I
mean they've been Christians since the
time of Christ and the Drews is they're
a big minority too right that's right
the Drews are in Southwestern Syria and
they and they're all on the road
carrying their belongings on their backs
trying to get out too now I mean John
when you first heard about the from
idlib is where a lot of them came from
right for this to over to final
overthrow the speed of it and how rapid
it was in the back of your mind where
you're
like what the hell I mean the Turks the
Turks hit the sweet spot so the the the
Turks could not have timed this any
better it's complicated right so the
Turks have long put pressure on Syria
all along that border it's a very long
very dusty desolate border order they
decided to leave the Syrian Kurds on
their own it's not worth going to war
because the United States supports the
Syrian Kurds so
outside the area of control of Syria's
Kurds is Turkish control now for all
intents and purposes Hezbollah has been
destroyed as a military force it no
longer exists it's a political party but
militarily it's done and I mean for like
at least the next six to 12 months it's
done
so they don't have to worry about
Hezbollah coming to the aid of the the
Assad government that solves a big
problem for Israel too and I'll get to
that in in a few seconds um number two
the Russians are bogged down in in uh
Ukraine they have bigger fish to fry
right now number three though and I
think this one is really
important the Israelis have repeatedly
attacked Iran in the last 18 months and
the Iranian responses have been very
very
soft you know can you imagine if
somebody if a foreign country blew up a
residential home in the center of
Washington and killed an invited guest
of the American government we would go
completely batshit crazy launching
rockets at
everybody and the Iranians are like oh
dang the Israelis uh killed isia dang it
right in the center of Teran well now
what we going to do oh well we'll find
somebody to replace fire a potato gun
atam fire a potato gun which is exactly
what they did the Israelis the Israelis
bombed the Syrian the sorry the uh
Iranian Consulate in Syria which is a
violation of international law the
Vienna convention they killed two
generals and the Iranians are like ah
dang H we should probably retaliate
let's send 700 slow motion drones and
warn the Israeli government in ADV
advance that they're coming to allow
them to shoot down 693 of
them so the Turks calculated we do this
the Russians aren't coming in Hezbollah
can't come in the Iranians are afraid to
come
in and nobody's going to stop us and
that's exactly what they did and then as
soon as the Israelis saw that the Turks
are doing all the heavy lifting for them
they have moved into Syrian territory
with tanks viol ating the 1974
non-aggression paack that they had with
the Syrian government and as of four
hours ago which was the last time I
checked the Israelis have bombed
350 military sites around Syria wow 350
sites and what's the Russian reaction
the ministry of of Defense of Russia
yesterday released a St statement saying
that they hoped that the new government
of Syria would respect the sanctity
of Russia's military bases in the
country and they're like uh no we're not
and they took everything except the Navy
base so far wow and then ass Assad shows
up at the palace with Putin and another
thing too a week ago Saturday Assad and
his entire family went to Moscow and
there were some Rumblings oh is he
fleeing why why did he take his family
he met with Putin came straight back to
but left his family in Moscow and then
over the course of the week last week
there were four flights with the same
plane between Damascus and Moscow
apparently taking plane loads of cash
his personal possessions
artwork and then ah he just runs away
poof it's all over wow yeah it's funny
because there's a lot of footage of
people looting the palace and they're
stealing all these nice ornate chairs so
maybe they got everything else out
before I suspect so because I'll tell
you what those chairs you can get for
$150 in the suit Nancy Pelosi had better
ones on
j6 she had exactly the same side table
they're all over the place you can get
them everywhere you can get them
everywhere they had their own little j6
you
know yeah it's it's just so wild so I
mean propping up all these Rebel groups
and there's what five or six really big
ones yeah would would you say yes
a group of of what they call um
independent resistance that's kind of
makes a semicircle around the US
presence okay they're just they're just
former Al-Qaeda people that that we pay
now in in your estimation John is it is
it uh British intelligence the Israelis
in America who really are the ones
funding and getting the resources and
the training and the weapons to these
guys yeah it's primarily the United
States uh and turkey uh the Israelis do
it a little bit more indirectly but yeah
you you've hit it on the head and and I
would even say that the French
intelligence service is probably in
deeper than the British are really yeah
because Syria and Lebanon used to be
French colonies and the French still
like to keep their hand in things okay
so so I add one other thing I'm sorry
Mike to interrupt you I wanted to I want
I've I've written this little anecdote
uh in the past but I think that it kind
of puts things into perspective when
um when I got divor wor in in
2000 I had my kids for a long weekend
and they really really wanted to go to
see a WWE show so I got tickets in
Madison Square Garden and so we're
watching you know Smackdown is what it
was and I don't know what the heck's
going on so my oldest at the time was
uh he was like eight or nine and I said
to him I said buddy I I don't understand
which one is the good guy and he said
well that's just it Dad there is no good
guy and that's the situation in Syria
there is no good guy so it's not like uh
you have to intellectually struggle
through this to figure out which one's
the good guy which one's the bad guy
there are no good guys they're all
murderous tyrants all of them it's just
that some are slightly less murderous
than others that's what I said to you
Mike on the ride home today I said none
of them are good and and Trump trump was
saying people are getting their heads
chopped off and Jeb Bush wants to talk
about my tone okay I mean Ser did you
see Trump's post on Truth social I
shared I shared it everywhere and I said
this this is why I publicly supported
Donald Trump this time around if just
for this and he sticks to this we do a
little bit better the next four years
yes agreed do you feel that way too John
don't get involved they're not our
friends it's not our fight don't get
involved you know galani oh galani there
John he was just a a little bit Al-Qaeda
when he was 19 when we're teenagers we
all go through an Emo or a goth phase
could it be could it be that Al-Qaeda
was a goth phase when he was 19 do you
think he's he's shaken it or do you
think he's still pretty big on on the
al-Qaeda in the 911 I would say that
when he was the number two in Isis that
may have been his goth phase yeah as an
adult he ended up heading
Al-Qaeda he was born he was born in
Saudi Arabia to Syrian parents from the
go
Heights that's exactly right you know
and you know you guys know the depth of
the hatred that the Saudi royal family
has had for the Syrian government for 50
years goes back I wonder how much I
wonder how much of this guy's logistical
money has come from the Saudi royal
family because nobody's talking nobody's
saying a word about Saudi Arabia well
that's that's a really good point yeah
what is yeah where where does Saudi
Arabia play in all this that's a really
good point yeah they're just kind of
like
you know like we're supposed to think oh
yeah oh no they don't have anything to
do with it they haven't made any
statement that's nonsense and you know I
I feel badly for the jordanians because
they have yet more Chaos on their border
right on their feel bad for the
Egyptians because the Egyptians are like
well now we don't have enough to worry
about with all these Palestinians trying
to cross over yeah now we have to worry
about all hell break and loose in Syria
right exactly what a what a mess yeah I
mean you know it's like if Trump can
just obviously I think it's hyperbole to
say I'm going to get this thing solved
in 24 hours John I mean that's it's
although since he's been president elect
things it seems like China wants to come
to the table Israel wants to come to the
table um Putin so it's almost like
Optics can can lead to something we can
almost will something good into
existence and maybe keeping the nukes in
the silos you know instead of flying and
that's that's what I'm hoping for at
that this point with you like I'll
support the candidate that that that uh
doesn't think that there's a good
outcome for any nuclear weapons uh
hearing some of these military people
who go on TV who say well if it was like
a limited nle you know if one nuke went
off you know and it might maybe it'll
kill five or 10 million people
ultimately but we we can win that
nuclear exchange and I'm just thinking
to myself these people sound exactly
like lame in the same psychopath that
were around Kennedy in the early 60s yes
yes Pat Buchanon of course a nuclear war
is winnable it's like what on What on
what planet are you talking about you
know and back to the ones that are
criticizing Tulsi and trying to come out
against her I think there's a lot of the
same names who are on the list that said
that the hunter laptop was just Russian
Intel so I don't think those people or
those voices have any credibility
anymore John I don't know zero zero now
this is where Trump aired in the first
term he talked about draining the swamp
and he's gonna kill the swamp monster
and he perpetuated the swamp he promoted
the swamp monsters you put the likes of
bloody Gina haspel in as the CIA
director or Mike Pompeo as the CIA
director John Bolton as the National
Security adviser are you out of your
mind but now I think it's different I
have a friend who's very senior in in a
a major State Republican party and he
told me the most interesting story over
the weekend he said that he was in the
room when Trump was first sworn in right
he had been president for a week or two
he was in the room um and Trump was
talking about he asked he asked a
general who was there in the room what
would the Fallout be from a US nuclear
strike on North Korea he said if I
decided a bomb North Korea right now
what would the what would the political
Fallout be and the general is explaining
the Fallout and then the National
Security adviser at the time it was um
General uh
oh I no
Flynn it was right after Flynn left so
it was a month
in I forget now but anyway um he said
well Mr President you would have more of
an
impact if you tried to make peace with
the North Koreans it would be so
disarming they wouldn't even know how to
respond and that's when Trump came up
with the idea of the love
letter and it was historic wow it was
historic so we're not we're not dealing
with an idiot I mean you can like Donald
Trump or not like Donald Trump I
there're a lot of Donald Trump's
policies that I disagree with but he
actually is the peace candidate because
he's openminded
enough to listen to others opinions and
if he thinks it's a good idea he'll
adopt it as his own and I will say I
think that his and this is how we
started this conversation I think his
appointments this time around are far
better than they were the first term I
think tulsy gabard was an inspired Stick
it to the Man choice where you pick
somebody who really is going to shake
things up but is qualified and know what
she's doing and Ratcliffe John Ratcliffe
you know again you could like his
politics or dislike his politics but
he's an outsider with experience
right and you a known quantity in DC too
McMaster McMaster it was McMaster thank
you malberry
picker y yeah go ahead Mike what do you
what do you make John of the possibility
of uh amarillis Fox Kennedy being the
number two at the CIA have you heard
deputy director that's being floated yes
I heard that about four days ago and
aios reported it it was a little
shocking to me yeah me too but I don't
know if you guys I'm sure you guys do
know her yeah from the campaign I do I
was on staff with the campaign um for
about six or seven months and I've had
many meetings with amarillis and Bobby
um yeah I I know her I know her pretty
well I like and trust her I don't know
her I've never met her but she's got
experience and uh yeah I'll tell you
guys a funny story when I first got
hired at the CIA I was a junior junior
analyst and I got hired with a group of
analysts there were like five or six of
us and at the onee Mark um you go to
meet with your division Chief so you're
like a gs9 and he's an SIS three or four
so he's what is that uh six he's nine or
10 grades above
you and he always asks the same question
where do you see yourself a year from
now and I said I was the first one to
speak and I said well I hope to be an
acknowledged expert you know on on the
Persian Gulf uh not just acknowledged in
the agency but in the intelligence
Community I had already briefed the
president at that point the vice
president the Secretary of State and he
goes the next guy and yeah that guy
wants to be an expert and this guy there
was this older guy he was also a gs9 but
he was a linguist and um he said well in
a year I would like to have your
job and the division Chief kind of looks
at him and he says I've been here for 32
years to get this this grade and he says
well I don't think you're any smarter
than I am I think I could do your job oh
well the guy didn't last three more
months they ended up taking his badge
they escorted him to his car and told
him get the hell out and don't ever come
back but 10 years later I remember
reflecting on that meeting now once you
hit the 10y year mark in your career
that's where the men are separated from
the boys and you can sort of see who
going to make it into the senior service
and who's not at that 10year Mark I
remember reflecting back and
thinking he probably could have done the
division Chief's job it wasn't that hard
either you're good at managing people or
you're not some people are just born to
manage and some are brilliant and just
can't they can't manage out of a paper
bag Emerald as Fox left the CIA when she
was a gs12 or gs13 and she went into the
media and into documentary film making
and had a second career a second life
just because she left as a gs12 or 13
doesn't mean that she can't run the
CIA especially 15 years later with all
this
experience and so I hope she does get
this job I think that she would shake
things up and I think that she is
someone that the rest of us who used to
be in the agency and are now outside
looking in would consider a friend and
supporter right and what based on your
your experiences John what is the
primary duty of the deputy director of
the CIA ah yeah the deputy director is
the one who actually runs the day-to-day
operations of the CIA the director is
busy every day meeting you know
breakfast with the president and lunch
with the chairman of the Senate
intelligence committee and in the
afternoon you know briefing the
Secretary of Energy and then meeting
with the King of Jordan and then dinner
with you know the prime minister of uh
whatever the deputy director is the one
like going to the meetings making the
Personnel decisions making sure the
trains run on
time okay yeah so it's more it's more of
a
management and um staying on point and
on task and kind of directing where
things are going to go it's like
conducting it's like conducting and and
the CIA now has um an executive director
uh now it's the deputy it's called the
deputy director for I forget what
administration or something um that
that's not exactly the right title but
whatever it is it used to be called the
exter the executive director and so the
deputy director of the
CIA um sort of farms out to the
executive director all the budgetary
stuff okay so that guy does the budget
you do covert action major Personnel
changes who gets to be the chief of what
station in what part of the world that
kind of stuff the deputy director picks
that yeah okay so that's based on
probably relationships and interviewing
people who they find to be experts of
those regions of the
world or have experience or contacts or
have run in a perfect world
usually like let's say you started off
as a case officer and you served and I'm
I'm just going to make these up this is
not an acknowledgement that there are
stations in these places I'm just saying
these as an example let's say you start
off your first tours an i ababi then you
go to Cairo and then you go to
headquarters and then you go to Rome and
then you go to Kuwait and each time you
you're getting promoted little by little
then you go back to be a branch chief
and then you become a station Chief well
you've spent most of your career in the
Middle East so the deputy director is
going to look at your your uh file and
he's gonna say oh this guy belongs to
the near East Division and has spent
most of his career in the in the Middle
East let's make him station Chief in
let's say Tunis and if he does well in
Tunis he can come home and be the deputy
chief of you know counterterrorism let's
say or whatever so you have to have
some you either have to have some
experience specific to that region or
you are such a great manager that you
just go from Giant Station to Giant
Station because you're really great at
leading
people interesting so in that position
do you think emirus would uh be able to
really go in and find the file and and
shake up a couple of Skips because
obviously that's what Bobby wants her to
do in my that's what he wants her to do
I would actually ask you if you think
she has the ability to stand up to very
powerful
men uh I mean if if if her book is to be
believed and and I know I think that she
released her book without clearing it
with the agency or or there there were
some issues with that love that I love
that major guts punk rocker so that's a
ballsy thing to do but I think I think
she needs to know what she's looking for
because obviously they're going to try
and um off escate and I want to see the
the Joan stuff I want the am Spell
document on Oswell on Oswald um but I
wanted to ask you though John but before
we go back into that I I don't think the
CIA is gonna have a document that says
oh this is what this really was this is
who they're not gonna write down no like
there there's there's no Smoking Gun
document no but I believe the CI still
wants to clutch those files because the
researchers are so goddamn good at at
piecing stuff together that they can
have a bigger picture of it's called
It's called The Mosaic concept where you
just take these little tiny tiles and
you put them together and they actually
give you an entire picture I asked Peter
Dell Scott about a year ago I said we
were talking about the both the Trump
Administration and the Biden
administration's failure to release
these 10,000 documents and I said to him
I said I'm gonna make an educated guess
here and I'm going to say that those
documents pertain specifically to CIA
surveillance operations in Mexico City
in
1963 and he said I think that's exactly
what they're about so I said I said well
60 years have passed who gives a
who the CIA was surveilling in in Mexico
City in 1963 and he said that's not the
question the question is was the CIA
surveilling Lee Harvey Oswald in Mexico
City in 1963 and the CIA doesn't want us
to know the answer to that question well
according to Jefferson Morley they had
five different things opened up on
Oswald before November the 22nd
including the am spell with the Dr with
George joanes right which was the first
group to release any public information
about Oswald after the assassination to
try and paint him as this rabid Castro
supporter yes and of course I think we
talked about this in the prior show but
Joe Anis was joanis was the guy who who
told the house select committee what
they could look at and what they
couldn't look at in the 70s but he
failed to mention that he was involved
with these student groups and the Castro
stuff and what he knew about OS I'm
ashamed to say that the guy's Greek
American because you know just as a
general rule we we try to all stick
together and support each other but this
was one very bad man yeah did you ever
did you ever meet him did you know him
nope never he left before your time he
he died in the 90s or 2000 yeah he left
in like 75 I'm gonna say he he was an
earlier generation he was out way before
you were in and you know it's funny too
because there were a lot of guys from
that generation like legendary names
that everybody used to talk about like
for example James Angleton when I got
hired people were still talking about
Angleton and how scared they were just
to walk past him in the hall you know
nobody ever mentioned um
joanis nobody ever yeah Engleton was
more yeah they called him mother and he
was always hunting the mold and some
people thought he was the mold and you
know that's the paranoia you know that's
some of the we we could have a whole
two-hour show just talking about the
Angleton
we should we should do that future I'll
tell you a quick story I told this
recently on a on a podcast um actually
no I told it on my uh on my show on my
my TV show um when I was uh I was
stationed in Saudi Arabia in 1991 after
the Iraqi invasion of Kuwait and I was
invited to uh to to dinner at the house
of a member of the Saudi royal family
and it was a whole bunch of people must
have been a hundred people so I see this
guy and he you know sees me you know
you're just making the rounds chitchat
so he introduces himself as Abdullah
filby and I said nice to meet you abdah
I said you have a kind of a famous name
there was actually a famous traitor by
the name of of philby Kim philby and
that's how I said it there's a famous
Traer by the name of and he says he says
Kim was my brother we don't we don't
talk about
Kim and I said oh I'm so sorry I said
I'm sorry I didn't mean to offend you he
said no
he says no offense I said do you mind if
I ask you how how could Kim philby be
your brother if you're Saudi and
Muslim and he he told the most
interesting story their father was a
doctor and he was the personal physician
to King abdulaziz iban saoud the founder
of Saudi Arabia and he served I saoud
Faithfully for decades now he had had
his family with a British wife including
Kim he divorced her moved to Saudi
Arabia was the king's personal physician
the king gave him a wife a Saudi woman
and the doctor converted to Islam and
had a second family wow and Abdullah was
from the second white holy I mean
that kind of makes sense though so that
was legit he was legit it was Kim Phil's
half brother
much younger brother right much younger
he was I'm going to say he was probably
20 years older than me yeah and and at
the time I was in my 20s I was like
2 six or seven so he was he was probably
50 wow yeah but small world you just
never know and I want to get more
information on Alan dulles's
relationship with um Ruth Payne's family
and Michael Payne's mother's friend have
you have you heard any of those stories
I've heard a couple of them but you my
just as a rule of thumb you should
believe every every horrible story you
hear about Alan Dulles and uh and about
John Foster dullas because they're more
than likely true monsters monsters both
I did an episode of my TV show on um on
the United Fruit Company and how how the
United Fruit Company like when the
government of Guatemala said hey you
know you guys are making billions of
dollars uh from our bananas and our
people are starving so we're thinking of
maybe you know nationalizing part of the
company our Benz yeah our bz and then
the the United Fruit Company overthrows
the government installs our b as the
military dictator but did you know that
John Foster Dulles Allan Dulles and
President Eisenhower's secretary's
brother were on the board of directors
of the United Fruit Company that coup
gave rise to the term Banana Republic
right Republic
right exactly and and so that arguably
the number one or number two person who
testified to the warrant commission in
1964 to bury Lee Harvey Oswald and
convince everyone of his guilt Ruth
Payne her sister was a psychiatrist for
the CIA for five years which she also
lied about and working on the
predecessor of MK Ultra right yes so so
there's there's a senator I forget his
name who said you know Oswald has the
Fingerprints of intelligence all around
him so I think uh he I think he was
probably being run around and uh um
maybe he was trying to infiltrate a plot
because the Chicago plot there was an
informant named Lee uh who warned about
what was going to happen and this was
three weeks before Dallas and it didn't
go down so yeah I think he was totally
set up and I think there's still a lot
of information out there that can can
illustrate that that could still be
released well I tell you what if if it's
going to be released it'll be this turn
these people that's
right that's right Bobby's committed to
it and and when Bobby endorsed Trump
there in Arizona after he suspended his
campaign in August Trump said there on
stage in front of everybody um I'm gonna
have a special uh commission
presidential commission on
assassinations and we're g to get all
the files out so we got to hold Trump to
that and we got people we got now people
around Trump and Bobby and amarillis and
Tulsi um and even vake had V ramaswami
on this show that guy actually knows his
stuff pretty well he's a pretty sharp
Fant he's a pretty sharp dude he's a
sharp dude yeah doge is yeah do you
think uh do you think John it's possible
for the Parton do you think the paron
could get some more legs your Parton uh
maybe not through Rudy
but not through Rudy look I can't go to
John I can't go to an ATM I can't buy a
hair dye I can't I can't get cash I
can't get Uber I wanted to punch him in
the face it has to be a business
expense yeah did you know that his dad
was a was a muscle guy for the Gambino
family yeah I knew his dad was connected
to the Mob I didn't know the specifics
yeah
um I I don't want to say too much but
you know Bobby tweeted um that on his
first day as president he would pardon
Julian Assange Ed Snowden and me I
remember that tweet he's been very kind
to me I will admit that he's not
answered my most recent uh uh text but
the guy's busy I'm a little busy right
now I'm busy right now John and a Budd a
buddy of mine is his he's a member of
the transition team is his handh holder
and so he told me hey buddy you know
we're we're busy right now so just be
patient um I have some I have some very
important uh
supporters you know what I should
probably leave it there yeah uh I'll put
it this way I I'm I'm very optimistic
that's what that's just what I wanted to
ask because that's how I feel too the
first time we sat down with Tulsi John
we asked her we brought your name up and
she said she was gonna look at it so I
think tosy knows who you are too no she
definitely does thank you I I hope so I
I I have always liked her and respected
her um she and I both spoke at a at an
anti-war event oh year ago February um
and I tried to chat her up I was there
with um Dennis cinic and uh I don't know
I I don't want to get my hopes up too
much just
because I'll I'll invariably be
disappointed but you know when Donald
Trump talks publicly about about
pardoning Julian Assange and Ed Snowden
I I know I'm a part of that
conversation yeah yeah and any anything
Mike and I can do anytime we have
anyone's here I we always bring up your
story and I say if I can pick someone to
get pardon it has to be John Kaku to
fredal prison for two years for standing
up and having some huge balls and
courage and uh doing the right thing you
know that wasn't easy and uh thank very
much I appreciate that it shouldn't be
forgotten um so you know we mentioned
deputy director of the CIA now you're in
your view the Director of National
Intelligence if you had to explain to
someone who has no idea what they do
what is the Director of National
Intelligence do the Director of National
Intelligence is in charge of the overall
budget for the entire intelligence
community and what is called the overall
OD for the community that's the
operating directive
so dni sounds like it's senior to
director of CIA the director of the CIA
is a more important position but it's
almost like comparing apples and oranges
so what the the dni does is the dni you
know in the beginning the dni had a
staff of 15 and now the dni has a staff
of more like
8,000 it's grown rather quickly and
unnecessarily yeah so they've
transferred a couple things from CIA to
dni like the president's Daily Brief is
now nni publication that's cool because
everybody should not everybody but Cia
Dia NSA and um INR State INR ought to
have the ability to write for it it
shouldn't be a CIA exclusive publication
now it's not
budget the cia's budget is you know the
the import of the cia's budget is 98%
everybody else is 2% so odni has
authority over that but the operating
directive is really really really
important so
um so it goes from zero which is the
most important to five which is the
least important so zero means they're
coming over the wall we got to do
something right this second so tier zero
would
be
um war in the Middle East Russia Ukraine
China tier one might be nuclear
proliferation
counterterrorism you know
Iran tier
two uh is going to be that next level
down Cuba
Venezuela whatever and then three means
ah if you get around to it four means ah
there's an analyst down the hall who's
interested and five means don't waste
your
time so it's the it's the dni who all
year long is going through hundreds of
thousands millions millions of
cables um liasing with cabinet members
and sub cabinet members to try to get to
what every person what every
stakeholder has uh on his or her plate
that the intelligence Community can
collect
on it's more of a coordination position
than anything else coordinator and
you're you're overseeing and maybe
trying to Corral the 17 intelligence
agencies yeah the they have this uh this
position they had this position at the
CIA called uh the National Intelligence
Council and the members of the of the
Nick were called National Intelligence
Officers nio so you have a National
Intelligence officer for the Middle East
one for Russia one for China One for
Latin America one for Africa one for
warning one for proliferation one for
terrorism um and then there's like one
for Europe and one for Southeast
Asia those have all been transferred to
the to the
odani and so what they do is they'll
write something called a sense of the
community memorandum or a National
Intelligence estimate or a special
National Intelligence estimate and time
used to be where those were written
exclusively by CIA or INR and now
anybody in the community can write them
because they're all going to be
coordinated by the dni anyway so it
actually has opened things up to to more
outside the box thinking you know this
is a longtime problem at the CIA you
have very smart people who went to the
best schools in the country and then
they engage in this group thing where
they all sit around the table and and
agree with everybody and I oh I'll tell
you what they do they get siloed I
remember you you use some Junkyard Dogs
sometimes in there as you know junkyard
dog man you need a blue caller Jun car
of dog you need a bomb thrower like you
know gust aotus used to be back in the
good old days but I remember sitting
there watching these two guys I was
sitting there like this watching these
two guys argue over a word we're like 45
minutes arguing whether it should be
happy or glad it's like guys I'm not
doing this anymore I don't care
what the word is and neither's the
president when he reads this stupid
paper yeah you know so that's odni now
so so DNA I will is one of the only
cabinet members though I have this right
that it does a pdb like a daily briefing
of pus correct every day every day six
days a week toy she'll be going in there
briefing Trump every day on all of this
she will be sitting in on the briefing
the uh the pdb staff has a director um
and the director is also the editor of
the pdb he always is the president's
briefer is that that's what Ray McGovern
did for 27 years right that's what Ray
McGovern did Ray Ray did it for two
years uh it took the other I'm sorry he
was in for 27 years right yeah took it
took the other 25 to work his way up to
that if you're an analyst you know if
you're an analyst and you're not the
deputy director for intelligence that's
the job you want that's the most
important job in the director yes
presidential Daily
Brief yeah because I mean if Tulsi does
get confirmed she she will have the she
will have the ear of the king six days a
week so will Marco Rubio R and so will
some of you made that point in your
piece John so brilliantly
Neons you need somebody who's tough
enough to stand up to these neocons I
think she is man I know she is she is I
think so too I think I know she is an
inspired
Choice yeah yeah I know she is I think
even even a lot of people in The
Establishment are like holy we
really do got to try something different
man this this is bad another billion for
Ukraine even the average Americans who
don't pay attention to this are
tired of all this so you know this is
why I this is why I support you guys are
gonna think I'm nuts this is why I
support the nomination of cash Patel to
head the FBI okay I probably disagree
with cash Patel on 99% of the issues but
you need somebody who's going to rip
that place down to its bare
studs scatter everybody out all over the
country rebuild it and then make them
stick to the uh to the original uh
reasons for even creating an FBI in the
first place to their Charter yeah and I
think that they're GNA find jer jer
Hoover's dresses they're going to find
the dresses I mean it's time I think
they are let's get them out there you
know that's right let's just be honest
with ourselves it's it's 2024 we can we
can Rebrand Jer G Hoover as woke you
know that is right there's a great
moment in that movie uh J Eder by Clint
Ewood I don't know if you've seen the
film I have yeah where he's you know
he's like looking over from his office
at at the next inauguration and the next
inauguration and he he was in there for
what eight or nine different presidents
yeah he was he was there for 48 he was
director for 48
years so which is nuts you know this is
kind of what I tell people like
presidents are they come and go
but I'm sorry to interrupt you Mike my
my next my next book um which has been
delayed for two years for reasons that
are not clear to me it's about
Washington DC historic cemeteries and
one of the most interesting stories in
the book is about Jay Edgar Hoover's
grave at um at Congressional Cemetery in
uh Southeast Washington do they give the
flag to Clyde Tolson is that true or the
house like uh Clyde Tolson lived next
door but he really just owned the house
next door they lived together and then
when Hoover died he lived in Hoover's
house and was the executive of Hoover's
estate they clearly lived as a married
couple I mean before before it came out
that Army Hammer was kind of low-key
cannibal I thought that was a great
performance as Clyde Tolson agreed
agreed well I'll tell you one of the one
of the things in the cemeteries book he
uh Hoover's buried in Congressional
cemetery and
um and they Buri him in kind of a
prominent uh place
so there's a famous um oh my God his
name is escaping me right now he was an
an army officer and he outed himself as
a gay man in 1976 and was on the cover
of Time Magazine and all it said on the
cover it was just him standing there and
it said I am a
homosexual so wow he forced the Air
Force to dismiss him and then he sued
Air Force and he won and it went all the
way up to the Supreme Court and he won
um but he ended up taking a payment a
payoff payout Leonard matlovich thank
you Leonard matlovich so um Leonard
matlovich in
1982 um contracted AIDS and that was a
death sentence in 1982 they didn't even
call it aids at the time they called it
gay cancer and
so just to stick it to Jay Edgar Hoover
he decided to buy a plot as close to
Hoover as he could get and so he died in
1986 I think it was and is buried just
he's actually buried like two two graves
from Clyde Tolson and about eight Graves
from from Hoover but because Leonard
matlovich was such an iconic important
figure in the gay rights
movement about 250 other gays bought all
all the plots in the area wow and now
Hoover is completely surrounded in
called in what is called the gay
quarter in there's even a historical
marker the gay quarter it's the first
specifically gay area in any Cemetery in
America and and J G Hoover's right smack
in the center of it did they send Harvey
Milk there is is he buried there Harvey
milk's buried there yeah oh man lindsy
lindsy Graham has to be buried there
with honors John with high H right like
I Beed there one who think that that
lindsy Graham's gay right well look if I
become President John my sister gonna be
first lady okay we gonna drink ABS my
sister then my mother and then some
another woman from the debutants ball
will be first lady exactly wow I never
heard that story did you hear the story
about the the comedian who bought a plot
next to Lee Harvey oswal grave no so
when you go down to Fort Worth to the
cemetery where Oswald is buried and you
ask at the front you know we're I want
to see the Oswald grave they don't tell
people anymore but this comedian bought
a gravestone with the name Nick beef and
there there is no Nick beef it's it's a
fictitious grave so if you ask for Nick
beef they'll point you where that is and
it's right next to oswalt's
grave okay thank you for that that tip
so John next time we come down to
uh um I'll take J Hoover is so he's not
in Arlington right he's not in Arlington
no no no yeah
yeah no
sir Congressional Cemetery he has a
different Eternal Flame you
know dude oh my God and it's it's in
such a great area it just just like 30
feet in front of him there's there are
these two obelisks they're for these two
sisters and I mean you look at them and
you say oh it's some 19th century
spinsters whatever no they owned the
most important the biggest poror house
in Washington it is now uh or it is what
is now the um uh Smithsonian Museum of
the American Indian it's right at the
foot of Capitol Hill so all the
representatives just walk down the hill
on their lunch hour go to the warehouse
and then walk back up the hill
and their house is now is now marry
Mount University in
Arlington wow Charlie Wilson had to have
had an office
there well hey you know there's there's
a new documentary about uh Lincoln
Lincoln's bunk me and how saying Lincoln
was gay have you heard that that story
that theory I heard that I I actually
read that you know I'm kind of a Lincoln
uh offici andado I I'm a Lincoln
collector I own a I own a blood soaked
scrap of the pillowcase that he died on
oh my God really yeah yeah you have
to follow the provenance it's all about
the provenance I own three strands of
his hair that the doctor pulled out to
get to the bullet to dig the bullet out
of his brain and I own ask how much you
spent for that yeah it's it's expensive
and I mean that was your first CIA
retirement went towards that yeah the
these are not these are not like from
eBay these are from sopes and these are
hor cruxes yeah yes with impeccable
provenances I own a I own a piece of the
of the Gallows that the that the
conspirators were hanged on and I've got
a I've got an 11 and a half inch strip
of wallpaper from the room that he died
in the only thing I ever got out bid on
and I kick myself this was like 10 years
ago was the the original key to his tomb
I I lost that I dropped out at 6,000 it
end up going for like 9,000 I just
couldn't that's okay yeah I mean it's
just a skeleton key you know I couldn't
I mean is is it true the bed was too
small to rest him on the bed was too his
legs were hanging over the bed they they
had to lay him diagonally on the bed
because his uh his legs were hanging off
one of the first things that really got
me interested in politics in American
history was a trip in eighth grade
called American Heritage Tour that we
took with another school and we actually
went to um Ford's Theater where where
Lincoln was sh it's it's magnificent
isn't it it's amazing that it's still
there and they got the box there with
the with the um it's like a red white
and blue uh flat bunting yeah bunting
I'll tell you one other thing too I went
to a I went to a museum with my kids
once and my wife in uh Baltimore and it
was called the sideshow Museum it's
defunct now and it was stuff from 19th
century sides shows and they had this
shadow box about that big with with a
turd a dried out turd in it and it was
Abraham Lincoln's last turd and they
said that the night that he went to the
theater you know he got there a little
bit late the show had already started
everybody when they saw him they stood
up and and clapped and then the show
went on that he discreetly excused
himself so he could drop a deuce and
then went back into the box and Booth
shot him so I'm like oh my God and I'm
taking pictures of it right like I I had
never even heard of this before it was
from some circus side
Sideshow well then six months later the
museum goes out of business and they
decide to auction off all the Holdings
and I said to my wife I'm buying
Lincoln's turd I'm buy she's like this
is absolutely not you have no idea what
the provenance is that's why you got
divorced that was why you got that one
one of the many reasons so I said I'm
buying it so it was it was the dookie
from CAD Shack it was the baby
roof bar there's like a there's like a a
grain of rice sticking out of it and um
and like historians will tell you what
his last meal was and it included rice
and I'm like okay if this is truly
Lincoln's tur I'm buying I don't care oh
my so I go to the auction online and and
I get out Bid And I'm like damn it like
what A Conversation Piece right but then
the buyer sent it for DNA
analysis and they found that the turd
had bits of Necco wafer in it you
remember neers when we were little kids
that's a more recent thing
1880 started making necro Wafers 1880
so I kept my five grand you
T yeah and my wife is like you idiot I
told
you there's no historical evidence that
he took a during the during the
play how would they I mean yeah we we'
have to get Al Jones analyze the
plumbing there at Fords that night folks
we'd have to look at what kind of
plumbing system they had how you get
access to it folks we we'll have Andre
Devonte look at it this is the thing
John this is what you know he does the
thing with his hands like this is the
thing Lincoln you know at the theater
where Lincoln was shot okay I can't
confirm this but I was only gs13 when
this happened so I'm not going to say
too much yeah like I like your Sideshow
Bob
hair like you're trying to be discreet
and you look like Sideshow
Bob he's undeniable rule number one do
not draw attention to yourself one time
I was sitting at a cafe in Athens with
the station Chief we were just doing a
little surveillance detection route and
we stopped at this Cafe and we're
sitting outside just having a beer and
these two guys start insulting each
other like your mother your sister you
know going back and forth and then one
of them like slaps the other one
across the the face and then much to our
shock the other guy that got slapped
pulls out a knife and instinctively I
stood up and my boss says what the
do you think you're doing did they teach
you nothing do not draw attention to
yourself and I sat back down and he was
exactly right and Here Andrew bante
looks just like Sideshow Bob he's very
cartoonish it's yeah I you're you're a
big guy what do you like 62 61 61 yeah
so you're you're not you're not like a
shrinking violet John so no you're
you're over there you know do you have
to put like the you like ever have like
a porn star mustache or oh yeah mustache
beard I had this I was talking about
this just recently on a podcast I had a
bald head with a comb over and it was so
perfectly done that the only seam was
right here on the bridge of your nose it
was before I wore glasses so they gave
me glasses with clear lenses that
covered up the seam I went into the
ambassador's office with a station Chief
and he said Ambassador I'd like to
introduce you to one of our experts came
from Washington and he says oh hi Hi how
are you nice to meet you and I said I'm
doing well thanks how are you he said
I'm doing well who are you here to see
and I go like this I go actually I'm
here to see you and I pulled it off and
he just
goes he his pants he's like oh my
God you guys always amaze me oh my God
now now doing a good impersonation is
that a good skill for an officer if you
can do a good like vocal or verbal
accent or impersonation without a doubt
I told a story the other day um was on a
plane once from Milan to Sophia Bulgaria
and I never talk to people on planes I
hate it I just mind my business I read I
just apologize because I take up two
seats because of my hat I just I'd like
to apologize in
advance so I'm sitting next to this
Italian guy who won't shut his
mouth really it yeah seriously wouldn't
shut up imagine so he says so what do
you do for a living and I was like ah
I'm in uh import
export and he said oh well what do you
import export and I was like H you know
whatever whatever I can make money on
well that sounds kind of
mysterious finally I go look I smuggle
women in cigarettes from Eastern Europe
okay you happy
now and he goes like this he
goes I don't think I approve I said I
didn't ask for your approval
shut the up
and then he just he sat there like this
the rest of the
flight it's like he didn't say anything
nothing not a word the rest of the
flight right so don't draw don't draw
attention to yourself John but there are
times you do have to Peacock a little
bit to kind of yeah kind of like keep
your keep your cover nip it in the bud
that's right Master of Disguise style
like Dana Carvey I think Dana Carvey
would be a good asset or an agent I mean
he's I'm not a fan of SNL now man but he
he brought the church lady back last
weekend it was phenomenal yeah
yeah just as good as it always was he is
and he he's almost 70 years old and he
still crazy and had like heart
replacement or open almost died yeah
something he he he had a lawsuit because
of that because the doctors messed up
his surgery and he almost sadly his one
of his sons just died a year or two ago
I think overdose overdose yeah I saw
that but he's a big inspiration for us
for like impersonations and comedy and
you guys you guys do it right you really
do
you know it I fooled my sister one time
I have to say I called my house one time
pretending to be one of my friends
asking for me and my sister answered the
phone and she thought it was my friend
so that's
great that was like back in high school
but Eric we got a couple chats here
we're over the hour mark I know we said
about an hour but um yeah you know we
got a couple chats for John or or
comments or I know you mentioned you
wanted to see some chats yeah uh they
know your Pennsylvania background John
can the Pirates do something in this
baseball Market
not so long as nutting owns the team you
know oh man listen I drive up to
Pittsburgh four or five times a season
to go see the Pirates I freaking love
the Pirates I don't care how bad they
are I just love the Pirates but now
we've got this kid this Phenom um who is
gonna win the sa young last year or next
year he just won the uh he just won the
Rookie of the Year uh this season um his
name is Paul skes this kid is a Phenom
he's going to be he's going to be you
know a Wan stto kind of kind of baseball
player but as a pitcher and the Pirates
are gonna do nothing to give him hitting
support nothing nothing so long as
nutting owns the team the the Pittsburgh
Post Gazette had an analysis of this the
other day where the Pirates have the
third lowest payroll in all of baseball
it's like $38 million but they take take
in like $56
million after all expenses and all that
money goes right into nutting's pocket
so why would he want to spend money to
make a real team when he's making so
much money now it makes me sick because
you know when I grew up north of
Pittsburgh it was in the 70s we won the
World Series in 71 we won the World
Series in 79 we made the playoffs like
literally every single year of the 1970s
these guys were Legends my first
baseball game that my dad ever took me
to Roberto Clemente was in right field
Willie starel was in left field Manny
sangan behind the plate I mean these
guys were Legends Hall of Famers now
they're just like jokes that just bounce
back and forth between Pittsburgh and
the minor leagues it's really sad so
we're not we're not they're not going to
do that well then this year you're not
you're not holding on hope no no you
know we always start off strong and then
just fade in August and September and
end up 10 20 games under 500 it's
embarrassing yeah the red the Red Sox
were 81 and 81 last season yeah you know
was pretty cool uh on Bobby's campaign I
actually worked and become good friends
with um a young fell he's
probably probably eight nine years
younger than me he's C Shy's grandson oh
how cool is that which which was cool
yeah yeah so that was I met I met ulyses
srant I 6th
wow he he is a plumber in St Louis
Missouri
really wow my ex-wife um spent a day
working with Teddy Roosevelt IV he's a
he's a banker on Wall Street how's it
related to Kermit and the fall Moji deck
yeah well you know it's funny that you
bring that up Mike because um Bob Shear
is a great friend of mine Bob uh is a
two-time Pulitzer Prize winner he was at
the Los Angeles Times for decades um
he's the one that did the famous
interview with Jimmy Carter during the
76 campaign and he got Carter to say
that he had lusted in his heart that was
like a headline if you can imagine it I
remember that well I don't I wasn't a
lie but I know the story you're talking
I know that particular
headline so um he told me when he was a
brand new
journalist he he told his wife I would
love to interview Kermit
and I want to ask him about madic and
the overthrow of the Irani government
whoa and so she said then call
him and he said it had never occur to
him just to find a number and call him
so back then all the news rooms in all
the big cities had um Telephone books
from all around the country so he gets a
Washington DC phone book and sure enough
here's Kermit Roosevelt listed in the
Washington phone book and he's staying
some he's living in some old folks home
up by the zoo so he calls him says who
he is I want to do an interview Kermit
Roosevelt had never done an interview
before but he was at the very end of his
life and so he decided for posterity
he's gonna do it and he gave such an
in-depth L uh in-depth interview to to
Bob Shear that Bob was able to tell for
the first time the unvarnished story of
the overthrow of the Iranian government
in 1953 now subsequently we've learned
that most of what Kermit said was
that it was actually the
British that overthrew the government
Kermit was the US liaison to MI6 and
Kermit Kermit was a was a media he
wanted to leak the story that he they
were dropping they were dropping
pamphlets and right and they were doing
riots and counter riots exactly that's
exactly what
happened yes
wow yeah he died in 2000
yeah that's kind he was
old he was born in 1916 it says here so
1916 to
2000 John what do you make of like e
Howard hunt at the end there was a
rolling stone piece there's his son St
John Hunt like I'm sure you're familiar
with him and with that do you think ye
Howard hunt was loopy full of or
you think he was being truthful and he
said that he was a benchwarmer for
Dallas I I think that I think that
Howard hunt probably had something to do
with it you know there's this natural
human need to come clean at the end of
your life unless you're some kind of
sociopath most of us have this need to
atone and um you know there
weren't rumors about Howard hunt going
back to 1963 for no reason right there's
a reason why he was always suspected of
having had a role in uh in Dallas and it
may not have been a direct role but I
think that what he confessed on his
deathbed we should probably take
seriously is there is there a CIA
historian or or something in conjunction
with the um CIA Hollywood liais on
office where when when people ask about
the Kennedy assassination or or or or a
famous oper event that like handles that
as like a PR person yeah what they do is
they just refer you to the office of
public affairs and then public affairs
will refer you to the um to the office
of the CIA historian which has a website
with all the the Declassified documents
which tell you nothing that will answer
your question but then they say oh look
how transparent we are we have 40,000
pages of documents on our website oh my
God is it tells us nothing no it doesn't
tell us anything I hear they have a
podcast now John have you heard that
they do yes they haven't invited you on
they have not invited me on but I will
say Just Between Us Girls here on the on
the podcast you're having more fun on
Jackman
radio that
my detractors at the CIA are all either
retired or
dead
and I never say no to a student who
wants to talk to me about career
opportunities and whether the CIA might
be right for them or wrong for them and
I give them the unvarnished truth well a
couple of them more than a couple about
a half a dozen have actually made it
through the process and are now at the
CIA oh that's great and they've told me
because I tell them listen I'm a realist
I would love it if the CIA ceased to
exist but it's not going to cease to
exist there's
always there are Patriots in the CIA
though I that and if you want to change
the CIA you have to do it from the
inside so now these half dozen people
are inside and
um and uh she said
that they've done a 180 on
me and it started when
bloody Gina haspel in her Senate
confirmation
hearings admitted that the torture
program was
illegal they told me I heard this again
just on Saturday that as soon as she
said that people felt free to express
their real opinions and she said people
have completely turned around on
you wow I mean deleting does of tapes
from black sites of torture is kind of
an admission of guilt
and being wrong being totally wrong in
what you did right so wow that's got to
feel good though John for you yeah yeah
yeah you know it did very much so and
I'll tell you another thing A buddy of
mine on Friday sent me a a buddy of mine
was taking a class at the Department of
Homeland Security and he said dude he
said you're famous here and he sent me
this this screenshot of a of a
PowerPoint slide and it says The Insider
threat and it has a picture of
me really seriously from his class yeah
idiots you know what was cool that I saw
and I think I even saw this since the
last time we had youan in Milford uh you
were actually a professor or teacher at
Jared Leto oh yeah I was Jared Leto's
High School history teacher and he came
back there later after he got really big
and famous and was like I I love you
let's do this interview like like yeah
you know like that's cool funny thing
about Jared he was freaking brilliant
Brant and I don't I don't throw around
the term brilliant I mean he was I I
said to him senior year he asked me to
write him a letter of recommendation for
film school right so I did and I said
Jared he said I want to be a I want to
be a director Mr kiraku and I said Jared
you're you're gonna be a success no
matter what you decide to do truly he um
he went to film School in
Philadelphia I went to the CIA I went
overseas came back on RNR in 1995 and
here's Jared on the cover of TV Guide he
was doing this show um my so-called life
he played like the really goodlooking
brooding quiet kid and he won an Emmy
and I was like oh my God Jared made it
and we we I ran into him on the street
once and we stopped and chatted and he's
like I know I can't believe it I'm like
I told you you're gonna be a success no
matter what you do and then I won when I
wrote my second book I won the uh Penn
First Amendment award it's a big deal
it's one of the big four with the pen
Falkner the Pulitzer and the Edgar Allen
Poe and they said well do you know
anybody famous that could give you the
award it's at the Beverly Hills Hotel
was the ceremony and I said yeah I know
a couple people I said um I said yoka
Ono might do it she's been really good
to me so they called her and she said oh
I'd like to do it but I'm kind of frail
now and I can't fly out to the West
Coast anymore it's just too much for me
so I said I said Oliver Stone would do
it in a hardbeat
and they said n we had Oliver last year
we want to try to mix it up and I said
well you know I was Jared Leto's High
School history
teacher so they said oh okay we'll reach
out we'll reach out to his uh his people
he said yes
instantly and um and he went and he he
did it it was great and then the next
day I went on his podcast went to he he
has a house in the Hollywood Hills and
and he's got a studio set up there so I
went wow what's funny is that that big
show my so-called life was with Claire
Danes who was Carri in
Homeland exactly right brilliant totally
act accurate about CIA John right
everything totally accurate totally
accurate the only thing that was
inaccurate was um if you go nuts they
send you away until you're not nuts
anymore you can't just go nuts and keep
doing the job you yeah you fail up
become station Chief and and yeah but
but Jared little also at one time owned
the lookout mountain out in um yeah he
still does lur Canyon you know like you
know Frank Frank Sinatra and Mar Monroe
had like security clearance to go there
and film stuff yeah yeah it was a Navy
facility it is it's absolutely enormous
it's like 100,000 square feet but it
looks like you step into a time capsule
it's right out of the 70s have you been
have you been there
yeah yeah wow it's a hole Yeah it's
it's gonna take aund million it's it's
California okay of course it's a
hole okay EXC sh excuse me it's Gavin
Newsome's backyard of course a hole
Yeah it's gonna be a hole we have
another question here I think we touched
on this in our first one was Phil uh
John B hello John was Philip Seymour
Hoffman character in SE Charlie Wilson's
War modeled after John K it was close
though close well thank you no the
Philip soroff Philip cofen character was
modeled after my mentor and friend gust
avatus and you know the only difference
between Philip Seymour Hoffman and Gust
in real life was that gust had a far
filthier mouth and was more violent than
Philip Seymour Hoffman Hoffman was in
the movie what time what time gust and I
were talking in the office oh I'll never
forget it
and I mean he and I were like this right
he was truly my mentor was like a father
figure to me and we grew up I mean I
grew up within 15 miles of his hometown
so we had the western Pennsylvania
connection and we're both Greek and you
know all that stuff we used to have
dinner together all the time but I said
one sentence I said malos was a torturer
now malos was the second victim of of a
terrorist group that we were working
against called revolutionary
organization 17 November he was also the
chief of the Greek National Police
during the military dictatorship and he
was a proud avowed torturer the United
Nations called him gree's head of
torture so all I said was malos was a
torturer he grabbed me by the shirt and
slammed me up against the wall and said
malos was my friend like
that and I said old man you better get
your hands off me or you're GNA
be very sorry
and then he let me
go and I said I know he was your friend
he was also a monster keep your
hands off me and then you know we went
to lunch together like everything was
fun and then after that you guys had
some peer bread some uh you know some
some good Greek nice Greek food and um
well that's it's interesting because
that's similar to kind of when you were
doing the debate um on concrete in
Buon his mentor and the guy that helped
his wife get in was a guy that you were
like well this is a guy who oversaw
torture who signed off on it or I forget
his name but yeah
yeah Bustamante is um misguided I'd like
to podcast I'd like to have him on you
think he'd come on yes I do yeah you
think he would yes we'll be nice nice to
him when was he in in the 90s or later
than that he's younger than a lot oh
he's a lot younger than I am yeah he was
there for seven years from like
05 to 12 or
well that would be interesting Mike
because we came of age in the war on
terror so we able to talk some with
him yeah love to you know Homeland
securi threat levels with uh uh you know
Ash coft and ridge that was very real
for us Mike red orange yellow yeah we we
trolled uh Tom Ridge at a Jeb Bush event
uh back in what 2015 Eric when was it We
snuck backstage after Jeb spoke because
Tom Ridge introduced him and we we had a
camera in front of Tom Ridge we didn't
film this part we filmed a little thing
with him but I said we filmed I said
could you say if you don't hi I'm Tom
Ridge and if you don't listen to Jackman
radio we're going to raise a terror
alert level to
Red he looked at me he's like he's like
I'm not going to do
that I mean John this is literally a guy
this guy was so scary to Mike
and I he's our Freddy Krueger he's our
Freddy Krueger because after 911 and
they created Homeland Security this is
the guy that's on TV day in and day out
blinking red
man for forest fires are at yellow today
oh they're at Orange oh they're at Red
like you know it's it's it seems comical
now but that's how we grew up so I I
remember when I was still at the agency
and they raised it to Red there was a
run on duct tape at Home Depot Jes and I
remember George tenant saying this is
ridiculous this is ridiculous we can't
keep doing this even tenant said that
huh yeah he had a Moment of clarity
these these colors didn't make anything
make uh sense
anybody that was clown World colors it
was just to scare people fire pixie says
John I got to ask what is John's opinion
the Fletcher
proudy she she was wronged wronged
wronged but not by the CIA by the
FBI well no Fletcher wasn't he the I
think he was a uh what was Fletcher
protar he was liaison to the Pentagon
and the like I'm sorry I'm sorry you
know what I'm talking about uh oh
back proty was uh southerland's
character in JFK was based oner I'm
sorry I I was thinking of of um the
woman someone else her name is proudy
hold on a
second um folks we do this live we do
this in real time we do it live like
Bill O'Reilly yeah it we'll do it
live she she was accused of being a
member of his Bala oh wow oh you don't
want you want to be that person Jesus 's
wife Gordon proud's wife uh her name was
not a proudy sorry not a proudy so I I
worked with her husband and um and she
she was a naturalized American of
Lebanese origin she joined the CIA had a
stellar career went to the FBI and they
um they picked up some
Communications where she was talking to
a cousin in Lebanon Hi how are you
what's new how's everybody how's the
family and then her cousin was married
to a guy who was a member of Hezbollah
well esbal is a legitimate political
party in Lebanon right right whether we
like their politics or not well the
reality of it and so they actually
revoked her American citizenship so here
she's a she's an FBI agent and a former
CIA officer and she is not any longer an
American citizen and she was stuck in
this no man's land because she's married
to a member of the senior intelligence
service
you know what do you do wow yeah that's
shitty awful awful
terrible yeah um oh and I'm looking at
fbi.gov ex agent proudy pleads guilty um
she plad guilty to fraudulently
obtaining American citizenship which she
used to get a job with both the CIA and
the FBI they they railroaded her
Fletcher proudy right he was the chief
of special ops um but
I I don't think he was at the CIA was he
he was the Pentagon he was a yeah he was
a pentagon guy who liaz Pentagon Intel
agencies on Covert Ops cover yeah
exactly Donald Sutherland betrays him in
JFK that's right on him yeah I apologize
I really don't know enough about him to
say anything F apologize I just wanted
to I was a audience uh question so I
wanted to make sure we asked it no
that's fine um but you know another
question I had John and you already you
don't have to tell the whole story and I
I I thought this story was hilarious and
I thought it humanized a certain former
president was Bill Clinton just being
chastised by Hillary when you were on a
trip and then you observed him going
down for afterwards being treated like a
rock star can you elaborate a little bit
on that yeah yeah so when I was
stationed in Greece um Bill Clinton came
for an official visit it was the first
official presidential visit to Greece
since Eisen how was President so this
was a very very big deal it was November
of
1999 and when you when you work at an
American Embassy and there's a
presidential visit no matter who you
work for everybody has to pitch in and
so the Ambassador just randomly assigned
jobs to everybody and my job that I was
randomly assigned was to be the
notetaker in Clinton's meeting with um
the Prime Minister the defense minister
and the foreign minister that's so good
together it it was a plum a plum
assignment dude that's epic for any
political science nerd yeah incredible
and you know the funny part was and I I
know you've heard this
um the meeting was held in the
presidential suite at the
Intercontinental Hotel on the top floor
overlooking Athens it's absolutely
magnificent and there was a gigantic
table that was just covered in food
right buffet that you could have fed a
hundred people and it was the prime
minister the defense minister the
foreign minister and their
notetaker President Clinton Secretary
Albright um Sandy Berger the National
Security adviser Ambassador Nick Burns
and me so it was nine of us so their
notetaker is standing on the opposite
side of the room I'm standing on the
opposite side of the room by the food
so they come in
and there are handshakes and hugs and
it's really warm and Clinton says to the
Prime Minister can I get you something
to eat and the Prime Minister says oh no
no thank you and the defense minister no
no coffee tea no no no no and then
Clinton turns to me and he
says may I offer you something to
eat and I said oh no thank you Mr
President I'm I'm good and he goes oh oh
are you with me and I said yes sir I'm
with you I'm your notetaker yeah and he
says oh I'm sorry I thought you were
Greek and I said I kind of am but not
really but I'm with you so then they do
the meeting and the meeting was so
devoid of any substance it was we love
you and you love us and you are the
birthplace of democracy and we have one
and a half million Greeks in the United
States and it's beautiful here and I of
it and then they went back and forth
like this and then they got up and gave
Big Bear Hugs and it was all great and
then the Greeks walked out so once the
Greeks walked
out Clinton and burger get up and walk
out go into the Hall
um Ambassador Burns and secretary
Albright walk out into the hall and then
I walk out last so I'm standing against
the wall just standing there and each of
these two groups um is about three feet
away from me so Clinton and burger
finished their conversation and burger
goes over to to Albright and burns so
the president and I are just standing
there and the elevator at the end of the
hall opens up and off comes Hillary and
Chelsea and
man Hillary's got this puss
like she just been shopping all day too
right
yeah spend taxpayer money yeah she walks
right up to us and she just stands there
she doesn't say anything one thing that
I learned about Clinton very quickly was
he hates silence he always wants to be
talking and joshing and joking and
laughing and yelling and and we're just
standing there so he says boy we sure
had a good time at the paron on this
morning didn't we
Hill she's just looking at him like this
now mind you this is this is months
after the Monica Lewinsky thing so she's
still pissed off it's bad so she doesn't
respond and he repeats himself oh we
sure had a good time at the parnon this
morning didn't we Hill and she says
Jesus Christ Bill it rained all day I'll
be in the room and she walks between us
she walks between us and then he looks
at me and he says let's get the hell out
of here
so he and I walk to the elevator the
Secret Service follows us everybody gets
the elevator we go down to the basement
and there are like 500 screaming women
down there it was the it was the Greek
USA Women's Business
Council and they're screaming like you
know
he's some kind of rock star or something
we love you yeah like the
Beatles and then he jumped right in and
gave one of the greatest speeches I've
ever seen in my life and I remember
thinking I of course I didn't say
anything because it's not my it's not my
place you know to to speak unless I'm
spoken to but I remember thinking my God
man you have to go to sleep to that
every night seriously yeah you actually
and you know Trump was like I actually
think Hillary is worse than Bill he does
she does the attacking and the ring she
does the the cover up she does the
Counterattack counter yeah she's way
more devious than he is the two of them
one two punch of the
clintons no I mean say what you will
about Bill uh you know awful he is or
whatever that's a great story John
that's a great story that dude has that
skill he he I've seen him work rooms
I've met him a couple times Mike you met
him here in Peterboro at the Town Hall
so he came here to Peterboro New
Hampshire and he was doing a town hall
for Hillary during the 2008 election and
um I I got the microphone and he called
on me to ask a question and I said
basically I said what if Hillary wins
what is she going to do to hold the Bush
Administration accountable for Iraq for
torture for everything and he goes I can
tell you're not passionate about that
that's that's the first thing he says
and he totally disarms the whole the
whole room laughs at me see what he does
he's good at it a friend of mine a
friend of mine was the head of
fundraising for Clinton for the entire
southeastern United States and he became
Clinton named him ambassador to
Luxembourg and now he's the president of
well I won't yeah okay he's the
President of recers University so anyway
he told me the greatest story he said
that when the Lewinsky uh story broke
all the finance people got together and
said we have to convince him to resign
he's got to resign let Gore be president
and then let G Gore run for his own term
he can't continue on his president he
might be indicted by the grand jury for
perjury he's got to resign and they all
met the night beforehand they rented a a
a small Ballroom like a meeting room at
the Willard Hotel across the street from
the White House and um and
uh Clinton came over so they're all
prepared he said it was like eight of
them they're all prepared to say Mr
President you have to resign for the
good of the democratic party for the
good of the country he walks in and he
says I have let you down
friends and started crying and the
Ambassador told me 15 minutes later
they're balling and they're shouting we
love you Bill we love you nobody ever
mentioned the word resignation and he
said we knew exactly what had happened
somebody had leaked to him what this was
about yeah and he's so good at work in
the room and disarming everybody he's
got a way about him oh yes he does so
John what what is in your opinion what's
the most accurate film depiction of the
CIA and why is it the Good Shepherd in
the
recruit yeah it it actually is the Good
Shepherd in the recruit oh is it I I
literally just pulled it out of my ass
now you know what I I just gave a very
very long interview to um to business
weekly for a documentary that they're
doing on spy films and we went into
depth I mean for hours I was there for
four hours we're looking at clip after
clip after clip the recruit the only
thing about the recruit that was
inaccurate
hair yeah that too actually no that
there are a lot of guys with hair like
that um it was that they didn't beat us
in
training that that was made up for
dramatic effect everything else was
spoton it was exactly right and then
um
uh what were we just saying um uh the
recruit and then good
shepher good sheeper because the Good
Shepherd was was historically based like
they used actual firstand
accounts first person accounts
documentary accounts to make that real
it it was it was right
on when when he finds out that his like
British Professor is MI6 or he's like
he's also with the SE and then they kill
him and throw him in the water you're
just like what the is going on but
that that crazy used to happen
during the Cold War OSS we and OSS we we
had a we had an agreement with the KGB
once the CIA was created in in 1947 we
had an agreement with KGB we won't kill
your guys and you don't kill our guys
and both sides really held to that the
KGB didn't have the same agreement with
other services and you know in fact when
Kennedy when Kennedy was killed the
first official communication we had from
any country was from the KGB and they
said we swear we didn't do this kof wept
yeah at when he was in line to sign the
book at Kennedy's funeral that that
that's what I've read I mean I think
Bobby even writes about that yeah in in
the American values book and I think
Jackie Kennedy even even said shortly
after we know it wasn't Cuba we know it
wasn't Russia because Fidel Castro's
first reaction when he heard was like oh
yeah so to go back earlier when you
were talking were they spying on Oswald
in Mexico
City I don't I don't think Oswald was
even in Mexico
City he couldn't he couldn't
drive he didn't have a
license so
supposedly he got there on a bus but I I
just I don't think like although there
was there is a CIA person who said um
her and her son their job was to
photograph Oswald or take video footage
of them or but let's see it I I guess I
want to reserve judgment before we see
if I based on my research I personally
don't believe Oswald ever went to the
embassies down there but I could be
wrong and I'm willing to admit that I
could be wrong I'd love to see these
documents I don't think there's any
legal reason for them to remain
classified yeah especially since
Congress has mandated that they be
Declassified and there is no legal
exemption from the mandatory
declassification act it was a law that
was passed in '92 so by 2017 they all
should have come out and it was actually
Mike Pompeo and Mike Pence that told
Trump not to do it not to do it yes so
bums bums if it was just oswal and
there's no conspiracy and it's three
shots from The Book Depository Kennedy
none of them should be classified
because they're all long dead right
exactly
precisely so yeah we want to get that
all out there and that's that's the hope
that we have with Trump and Bobby and
tulsy and everyone who's in there around
him and I'm with you John on cash Patel
I think that guy's gonna be a
ballc Crusher and a wrecking ball to all
that and and and you always say John
don't ever talk to the FBI do not trust
the
FBI they they will they will they will
you four ways from Sunday
they will you know what I want to read
you something if we have a minute I
apologize that we have gone so long no
well it's John you can do this as long
as you want to do it man we don't want
to waste your time looking forward to
this I will I will leave everybody on on
this note hold on one second audience
Loves You John jacman radio loves you
you're one of our favorite guests quite
frankly thank you I appreciate it the
only other guest who's been on three
times I think is Jesse ventor and Adam
Fitzgerald and we talked about great so
you're part of a uh good company yeah
you're part of yeah he's in the the
Greek Hall of Fame though Eric I think
he's the only actually John I think we
told you this my parents honey Mo was in
Greece I remember that we talked about
that 1984 so that it holds a special
place in my heart I love it ah here it
is I want to read this to you I received
this I received this as an email on
Saturday it says John it's nice to
finally speak with you I've been
watching your YouTube interviews and I
love all the content and I've been
wanting to reach out to you for many
years I'm one of the FBI agents who
would like to personally apologize to
you for the disgraceful way that the FBI
and our government treated you I worked
with both FBI headquarters and the
Washington field office on your case and
I know that many of I know many of the
Personnel that you're familiar with that
case was directed and driven by senior
officials it was a political case the
mid-level and Street Personnel were
against it from the beginning but
nevertheless we followed orders I've
always felt bad about that case and for
the way you were treated and I wanted to
personally apologize sincerely and then
he signs it whoa really you just got
that how do you like them apples that's
beautiful you know what the Tide's
turning everybody I think the Tide's
turning the you know what I think the
people are ready for truth we're ready
for a John kiraku Parton we're ready for
Tulsi D and I and we're ready for all
the Cy to come out no matter how it
lands let's let's have let's have a
Truth and Reconciliation and let's move
forward as a country Amen to that that's
thanks for having me you guys it's great
seeing you I only regret I'm not going
to be in New Hampshire until a couple of
weeks from now so we can't go out to
Milford again but I'd love it hey if
you're up here you're visiting family we
would love to take you out for a beer or
and I'll be with my son I'll bring him
too oh hell yeah awesome we got a great
Brewery here in our neighborhood we'd
love to bring you and your son too done
well John before we uh get off here log
off tell everyone where they can find
you and support what you're doing right
now ah thank you I put literally
everything that I do
um uh on substack so it's just under my
name John kiraku it's called loud and
clear with John kiraku or by John
something just if you just put in John
cuak it all pops up so thank you for
that awesome well folks thanks for
tuning in with us tonight it's always
fun with John and uh John is proof that
there are really good people who can
serve in our government there are
patriots on the inside people who want
to do the right thing and will do the
right thing so thank you for tuning in
with us hit that like And subscribe
button and if you want to support this
podcast
patreon.com Jackman radio and we will be
back again soon with another episode
thank you everybody and take care and
have a great night